Guide to the Merle Hoffman Papers, circa 1944-2012 and undated, bulk 1961-2000 RL.00557
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Choices Series, 1945-2000 and undated, bulk 1976-2000, 48 boxes
  - Subject Files Subseries, 1977-2000 and undated
    - Patient Information, 1970s-1998 and undated
      - Lodging for out-of-town patients, 1992-1994 and undated (Box CH8)
      - Pamphlets, 1998 and undated (Box CH8)
      - "Patient's Rights," undated (Box CH8)
      - Post-abortion instructions, undated (Box CH8)
      - Prenatal care, 1985-1988 (Box CH8)
      - Prostate cancer, 1994 (Box CH8)
      - "The STD Key," undated (Box CH8)
      - Russian language educational materials, 1992-1994 and undated (Box CH8)
      - Russian language forms, 1990 and undated (Box CH8)
      - Spanish language abortion forms, undated (Box CH8)
      - Spanish language educational information - men's health services, undated (Box CH8)
      - Translation services, 1998 (Box CH8)
      - Tubal ligation, 1992 and undated (Box CH8)
    - Research, 1981-1999 and undated
      - Adelphi Project (Box CH8)
        - Funding, undated (Box CH8)
        - Inventory and notes, undated (Box CH8)
        - Preliminary results, undated (Box CH8)
      - HIV Abortion Clinic Serosurvey, New York City Department of Health, 1996 (Box CH8)
      - Male survey on abortion, circa 1989 (Box CH8)
      - Marinoff, Lou, Philosophical Counseling, 1998 (Box CH8)
      - Mifepristone trials, 1994-1999 and undated (Box CH8)
      - Mifepristone trials, information kit, 1993-1994 (Box CH8)
      - Patient questionnaire form, circa 1994 (Box CH8)
      - Patient satisfaction questionnaires, 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box CH8)
      - Patient satisfaction questionnaires, 1992-1998, 4 folders (Box CH9)
      - Patient satisfaction survey results, 1999 (Box CH9)
      - Patient survey on abortion, 1989 (Box CH9)
      - Patient survey on abortion - press release and clippings, 1981 (Box CH9)
      - Patient survey on abortion, questionnaires and public reaction, 1982 (Box CH9)
      - Public Affairs Analysts, proposed research project, 1985 (Box CH9)
      - Responses to external surveys, 1991-1998 and undated (Box CH9)
      - Staff papers on rape and domestic violence, 1996 and undated (Box CH9)
      - Statistics and studies, 1992-1998 (Box CH10)
      - Vasectomy satisfaction questionnaires, 1991 and 1995 (Box CH10)
      - Women, Abortion and the Media - patient survey, 1985 (Box CH10)
    - General Subject Files, 1978-2000 and undated
      - Amniotic Fluid Embolism - lecture, 1997 July 18 (Box CH10)
      - Anesthesia articles, 1997 and undated (Box CH10)
      - Best, Winifred, documentary, 1990-1991 (Box CH10)
      - Choices Chatter, 1991-1997 and undated (Box CH10)
      - Choices Chatter materials, 1990-1993 and undated (Box CH10)
      - Choices Chatter puzzle contest, 1993 (Box CH10)
      - Choices Fund description and case records, 1989 (Box CH10)
      - Choices newsletter - "Choice Bits" cartoon, 1984 (Box CH10)
      - Clippings, 1978-1998, 5 folders (Box CH10)
      - Conference on women, Hunter College, 1990 (Box CH11)
      - Conference - National Latinas Caucus (1992), 1991-1992 (Box CH11)
      - Conferences - Parke-Davis, Trends in Women's Healthcare, 1996 and 1999 (Box CH11)
      - Depo Provera, 1992-1993 (Box CH11)
      - Domestic violence, 1989-1996 (Box CH11)
      - Female condom information, 1992-1994 and undated (Box CH11)
      - Frost's STD program, 1995 (Box CH11)
      - Gold, Martin - 80th birthday, 1998 (Box CH11)
      - Gold, Martin - memorial award, 1999 (Box CH11)
      - HIV/AIDS information, 1983-1996, 2 folders (Box CH11)
      - HIV statistics, New York City, 1993 (Box CH11)
      - Impotency booklet, undated (Box CH11)
      - Johnson, Karen, Women's health as a medical specialty, 1994 (Box CH12)
      - Lesbian and gay health information, 1993-1994 and undated (Box CH12)
      - Lesbian health project development, 1993 (Box CH12)
      - Morning-after pill information, 1993-1996 and undated (Box CH12)
      - National Women's Health Network, health information, 1990-1993 and undated (Box CH12)
      - Other New York clinics - financial statements, 1981-1982 (Box CH12)
      - Other New York clinics - mailing lists, 1992 and undated (Box CH12)
      - Other New York clinics - State Department of Health statistics, 1993-1995 (Box CH12)
      - Patient death, clippings and press release, 1994 (Box CH12)
      - Planned Parenthood conference, report on conference papers, 1994 Oct. (Box CH12)
      - Prenatal HIV articles, 1990-1994 (Box CH12)
      - Rape information, 1978-1992 and undated (Box CH12)
      - Rape Treatment Program - information on rape, 1990-1993 and undated (Box CH12)
      - Reproductive health laws and regulations - state and federal summaries, 1991 (Box CH12)
      - "The Victim Experience" handout, undated (Box CH12)
      - "Violence against Women Fact Sheet," 1990s (Box CH12)
      - "Wish list," 1993 Oct. 26 (Box CH12)
      - Zarkin, Dr. Allan, scandal - clippings, 2000 (Box CH12)
  - Legal Papers Subseries, 1978-1998 and undated
    Includes files on a variety of lawsuits involving Choices, contract negotiations, and other legal matters. Especially noteworthy are materials documenting Choices's long-term relationship with Health Insurance Plan of Greater New York, its disputes over Medicaid billing, and numerous statements of public support for Choices during an attempt to evict the clinic from its facilities in 1998. Files are arranged alphabetically.
    - Agreement with Health Insurance Plan of Greater New York, 1979, 1996, 2 folders (Box CH13)
    - Amicus curiae brief, Long Island Gynecological Services eviction case, 1996 (Box CH13)
    - Best Linen Supply breach of contract suit, 1989-1995 (Box CH13)
    - Bethea, Marvin (CPR training), 1991 (Box CH13)
    - Bylaws and share transfer agreement, 1995 (Box CH13)
    - Choices v. Health Insurance Plan - correspondence, 1993-1995 and undated (Box CH13)
    - Choices v. Health Insurance Plan of Greater New York, 1993, 3 folders (Box CH13)
    - Choices v. New York State Department of Health (Medicaid appeal), 1992-1995, 2 folders (Box CH13)
    - Choices v. Tri-Star Construction Corp., 1997-1998 (Box CH13)
    - Comprehensive Women's Health Care v. Blumstein, 1997 (Box CH13)
    - Contrux Construction, breach of contract suit, 1987-1996 (Box CH14)
    - Contract, T.L.C. Women's Services, 1992 (Box CH14)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1998 (Box CH14)
    - Gold, Martin, 1984-1987 (Box CH14)
    - Eviction threat - bound letters of support, 1998 Aug.-Sept. (Box CH14)
    - Eviction threat - letters of support, 1998 Aug.-Sept. (Box CH14)
    - Eviction threat - mass mailing requesting public support, 1998, 1 of 4 folders (Box CH14)
    - Eviction threat - mass mailing requesting public support, 1998, 2-4 of 4 folders (Box CH15)
    - Eviction threat - Notice of Petition for Eviction and legal complaint, 1998 (Box CH15)
    - Medicaid Fraud Control, proposed prosecution of Choices, 1988 (Box CH15)
    - Move planning, 1998 (Box CH15)
    - New York State Board of Health, notice of professional conduct hearing for Andre Nehorayoff, 1991 (Box CH15)
    - Partnership agreement certificate, Martin Gold and Leo Orris, 1978 (Box CH15)
    - Subpoenas for John Doe and Rolin Roe court cases, 1984 and 1985 (Box CH15)
  - Outreach Subseries, 1983-2000 and undated
    Documents Choices's public education programs and its relationship with other community organizations, especially those which served as referral sources. For more information on Choices's efforts to develop referral sources, see the Marketing Subseries. See also the files on managed care health insurance plans in the Legal Papers and the Operations Subseries. Arranged in alphabetical order.
    - Abelson, Gerri, outreach reports, 1994 (Box CH15)
    - Abzug, Liz, consulting services, 1996 (Box CH15)
    - Agreement - State University of New York Health Science Center at Brooklyn College of Nursing, 1994-1995 (Box CH15)
    - Agreements with other providers, 1993-1999, 2 folders (Box CH15)
    - Asian American social agency mailing list - "The Important Folder," 1993 and undated (Box CH15)
    - Association for the Help of Retarded Children agreement, 1993 (Box CH15)
    - City University of New York Medical School - site visit, 1992 (Box CH15)
    - CHOICE Hotline (Philadelphia), 1993-1996 (Box CH15)
    - Committee for Spiritual Healing and Empowerment (SHE) - correspondence and minutes, 1996 (Box CH15)
    - Committee for Spiritual Healing and Empowerment - domestic violence letter, 1996 and 2000 (Box CH15)
    - Coney Island Hospital agreement, 1994 (Box CH16)
    - The Door health center - letter of complaint, 1997 (Box CH16)
    - Education reports, 1990-1992 (Box CH16)
    - Elmhurst Hospital Center cooperation, 1995-1998 (Box CH16)
    - Garden State Medical Group, 1991-1992 (Box CH16)
    - Girl Scouts Outreach Program, 1983 and undated (Box CH16)
    - Health and Hospitals Corporation, 1993 (Box CH16)
    - Holliswood Hospital, 1993-1994 (Box CH16)
    - Jamaica High School, 1994 (Box CH16)
    - Latina outreach, 1990-1992 and undated (Box CH16)
    - Mailing Lists, 1995 and undated (Box CH16)
    - Mental Health Center Agreement with Elmhurst Hospital, 1995 (Box CH16)
    - Mental Health Center Community Breakfasts, 1995-2000, 2 folders (Box CH16)
    - Mental Health Center Community Breakfasts
      - Announcements and mailing lists, 1995-1996 (Box CH16)
      - Checklist of invitees and responses, 1995 Oct. (Box CH16)
      - Planning and attendance, 1995-1996 and undated (Box CH16)
    - Mental Health Center mailing lists - other agencies, 1995-1996 and undated (Box CH16)
    - Mental Health Center - support group flyers, 1997 (Box CH17)
    - New York City Department of Health - Women's Healthline, 1994 (Box CH17)
    - "Outreach Projects Update," 1985 (Box CH17)
    - Outreach reports, Patty Rosen, 1991 (Box CH17)
    - Planned Parenthood of New York, 1991-1997 (Box CH17)
    - Planned Parenthood of Orange-Sullivan (N.Y.) and Conn., 1993 (Box CH17)
    - Planned Parenthood of Pa., 1992 (Box CH17)
    - Planned Parenthood of Suffolk County, 1998 (Box CH17)
    - Planned Parenthood of the Susquehanna Valley, 1997 (Box CH17)
    - Puerto Rican Family Institute, 1992 (Box CH17)
    - Queens Festival exhibit, 1984 (Box CH17)
    - Queens Mental Health Council - minutes and mailing list, 1996 Jan. 4 (Box CH17)
    - Queens Teen Pregnancy Network, 1993-1994 (Box CH17)
    - Reproductive Health Services (St. Louis), 1993 (Box CH17)
    - Riker's Island correctional facility workshop, 1983 Nov. (Box CH17)
    - Samaritan Village in-service proposal, 1997 and undated (Box CH17)
    - St. Luke's-Roosevelt Hospital Center, 1993-1994 (Box CH17)
    - Victim Services, 1996 (Box CH17)
    - Women's Health Action and Mobilization (WHAM!), 1994 (Box CH17)
    - Workshop flyers, undated (Box CH17)
  - Personnel Subseries, 1945-2000 and undated
    Primarily documents the professional status, educational history, and licensure of Choices physicians and other medical staff. A few staff members have more extensive personnel files. Files are organized by name, with the individual's position in parenthesis. A small number of personnel subject files are located at the end of the name files.
    Files on general personnel policy are located in the Personnel subdivision of the Operations Subseries.
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Personal names in this subseries are suppressed in public versions of the finding aid. All materials, including access to personal names, will be open for research on-site, after the researcher signs an Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibilities and Privacy Rights Form.
    - Physicians' files (various names), 1945-1998 and undated, 52 folders (Box CH17)
    - Applications and resumes, 1990-1992 and 1996 (Box CH17)
    - Counselor evaluations, 1991 Jan. (Box CH17)
    - Loans to staff, 1996-1998 (Box CH17)
    - Loans to staff, paid in full, 1991-1997 (Box CH17)
    - Personnel file confidentiality codes, 1996 (Box CH17)
    - Resignation interviews, 1998 (Box CH17)
    - Salary grades, ranges, and personnel, 1988 (Box CH17)
    - Staff professional licenses, 1982-1983 (Box CH17)
    - Staff supervision log and in-service announcements, 1993 (Box CH17)
  - Security Subseries, 1978-1999 and undated
    Contains materials that record day-to-day security measures at Choices. In addition, documents the pro-choice movemement's attempts to combat anti-abortion violence and Operation Rescue protests in New York City. Choices staff was heavily involved in these efforts. The subseries contains files on a variety of pro-choice organizations and on Operation Rescue itself. Folders are arranged in alphabetical order.
    - Agreement on clinic demonstration guidelines, 1993 (Box CH20)
    - Attorney General's Task Force on Health and Reproductive Rights, 1994 and undated (Box CH20)
    - Bray v. Alexandria Women's Health Clinic, 1993 (Box CH20)
    - Bomb threats, 1987-1988 (Box CH20)
    - Bomb threat tactics, 1985 and undated (Box CH20)
    - Bomb threats/emergency procedures, 1992-1998 and undated (Box CH20)
    - Choices security manual, 1995, 1-4 of 5 folders (Box CH20)
    - Choices security manual, 1995, 5 of 5 folders (Box CH21)
    - Clinic access legislation, 1996-1998 (Box CH21)
    - Clinic defense projects - National Organization for Women (NOW), Feminist Majority Foundation, New York Clinic Defense Task Force, 1990-1992 and undated (Box CH21)
    - Clinic demonstration regulations, 1994-1999 (Box CH21)
    - Clinic Violence Surveys, Feminist Majority Foundation, 1994-1996 (Box CH21)
    - Correspondence, 1995 (Box CH21)
    - Counter Operation Rescue, 1988 (Box CH21)
    - Daily, Bishop Thomas, prayer vigils, 1990-1996 (Box CH21)
    - Facility threats, 1994 and undated (Box CH21)
    - Facility threats and heightened security measures, 1994 and undated (Box CH21)
    - F.B.I. directory, 1990s (Box CH21)
    - Guides to anti-harassment tactics, 1978-1986 and undated (Box CH21)
    - Injunction against illegal abortion clinic protests - memo, 1999 Aug. 3 (Box CH21)
    - Metro New York Providers meeting, 1995 Jan. and undated, 2 folders (Box CH21)
    - National Clinic Defense Conference mailings, 1990 (Box CH21)
    - National Clinic Defense Project, Feminist Majority Foundation, 1994 (Box CH21)
    - New York Clinic Defense Task Force, 1992 (Box CH21)
    - New York State National Organization for Women (NYS-NOW) v. Randall Terry, 1988-1993, 2 folders (Box CH22)
    - Operation Rescue and pro-choice response, 1988-1994 and undated, 3 folders (Box CH22)
    - Operation Rescue and pro-choice response, 1995-1998 (Box CH22)
    - "Operation Rescue - Philadelphia, July 4, 1988" - notes, 1988 (Box CH22)
    - Patient escort volunteers, 1993-1998 (Box CH22)
    - Patient harassment incident, 1982 (Box CH22)
    - Patient harassment - photographs and article, 1994 and undated (Box CH22)
    - Phone threats, 1991 (Box CH22)
    - Physician shootings
      - Choices reaction, 1993-1994 and undated (Box CH22)
      - Clippings, 1994-1995 (Box CH22)
      - Pensacola, 1994 and undated (Box CH22)
      - Pro-choice organizations' reactions, 1993-1996 and undated, 2 folders (Box CH22)
    - "Policing Demonstrations" article, 1989 Aug. (Box CH22)
    - Precinct police station, 1991-1997 (Box CH23)
    - Pro-choice organization newsletters, 1991-1993 (Box CH23)
    - Reiter, Fran (Deputy Mayor) - meeting, 1995 Jan.-Feb., 2 folders (Box CH23)
    - Schumer/Messinger clinic defense summit, 1995 Feb.-May (Box CH23)
    - "Synopsis of the Freedom of Access to Clinic Entrance Act," 1994 (Box CH23)
  - Staff Files Subseries, 1983-1999 and undated
    Contains working files kept by individual staff members relating to the day-to-day functioning of the clinic. Files are labeled by name, with the approximate job title or department shown in parenthesis. The files are arranged in alphabetical order.
    Choices organizational charts and staff rosters are available for reference in the Research Room's inventory files; please contact Research Services. For additional administrative material, see the Operations Subseries. Note that some staff members divided their time between Choices and On the Issues magazine; these individuals have staff files in both series. Statistical and marketing analyses in the Staff Files have been removed to the Oversize Material Series.
    - Abelson, Gerri (Director, Mental Health Center), 1996-1997, 3 folders (Box CH23)
    - Aisenberg, Karen (Executive Assistant), 1991 (Box CH23)
    - Capanzano, Maryann (Director of Quality Improvement), 1993 (Box CH23)
    - Eagan, Janet (nursing), 1991 (Box CH23)
    - Farrell, Annette (Executive Director), 1991-1998, 1-10 of 16 folders (Box CH24)
    - Farrell, Annette (Executive Director), 1991-1998, 10-16 of 16 folders (Box CH25)
    - Farrell, Annette (Executive Director), memos to review for weekly meetings, 1995 (Box CH25)
    - Gold, Dr. Martin, 1998 (Box CH25)
    - Hyduchak, Kristen (community outreach), 1996-1998 and undated (Box CH25)
    - Lengel, Kelly (administrative), reports to Joy Silver, 1996-1997 (Box CH25)
    - Matthews, Donna (Executive Assistant to Hoffman), 1997-1998, 1 of 2 folders (Box CH25)
    - Matthews, Donna (Executive Assistant to Hoffman), 1997-1998, 2 of 2 folders (Box CH26)
    - Michael, Jeannine (Director of Counseling/Consultant), 1991-1998, 7 folders (Box CH26)
    - Price, Sherry (Rape Treatment Program and Domestic Violence), 1992-1997 (Box CH26)
    - Rosen, Patty (Marketing/Outreach), 1991, 1 of 2 folders (Box CH26)
    - Rosen, Patty (Marketing/Outreach), 1991, 2 of 2 folders (Box CH27)
    - Safarian, Anastasia (Asst. Administrator, Patient Services), 1992 (Box CH27)
    - Sasso, Fran (Chief Financial Officer), 1992, 2 folders (Box CH27)
    - Silver, Joy (Marketing)
      - General, 1991-1999, 1-7 of 9 folders (Box CH27)
    - Silver, Joy (Marketing) (Box CH28)
      - General, 1991-1999, 8-9 of 9 folders (Box CH28)
      - Planning Committee materials, 1998 (Box CH28)
      - Referral source tracking and development, 1992-1995 (Box CH28)
      - Work updates, 1998 (Box CH28)
    - Singleton, Bessie (Quality Assurance/Risk Management) - memos, 1995-1997, 3 folders (Box CH28)
    - Stanley, Charlene (Computers), 1998 (Box CH28)
    - Walshe, Anne (Administrator) - memos, 1983 (Box CH28)
  - Marketing Subseries, (1981-1999 and undated)
    Comprised of materials documenting Choices advertising, brochures, and marketing plans. Marketing files also include statistics on clinic utilization, patient demographics, and referral sources. Files are in alphabetical order. Additional marketing-related material can be found in the Outreach Subseries and the Staff Files Subseries. See the Oversize Material for additional clinic utilization and referral statistics.
    - Abortion clinics internet directory, 1995-1996 (Box CH28)
    - Advertisement layout, 1984 and undated (Box CH28)
    - Airplane banner towing, 1993-1994 (Box CH29)
    - Annual report, 1990 (Box CH29)
    - Cable TV advertising, 1995 (Box CH29)
    - Chinese World Journal, undated (Box CH29)
    - Choices Calendar of Women's Wisdom, 1982 (Box CH29)
    - Choices notepad, bumper sticker, and information card, undated (Box CH29)
    - Information and publicity packets, circa 1983-circa 1999, 6 folders (Box CH29)
    - Letterhead design, 1998 and undated, 3 folders (Box CH29)
    - Logo - Choices and Mental Health Center, 1998 (Box CH29)
    - Managed care consultants, 1997-1998 (Box CH29)
    - Marketing firm proposals and estimates, 1997-1998 and undated (Box CH29)
    - Marketing plan, 1983, 1993, 2 folders (Box CH29)
    - Marketing plan, out-of-state, 1988 Oct. (Box CH29)
    - Marketing plans, 1987-1990 (Box CH29)
    - Marketing statistics - New York City population, 1993-1998 (Box CH29)
    - Memos and reports, 1990-1994 (Box CH30)
    - Mental Health Center depression screening ad, undated (Box CH30)
    - Mental Health Center information packet, 1990s (Box CH30)
    - National Abortion Federation subway advertising, 1999 (Box CH30)
    - New York Times advertising, 1998 (Box CH30)
    - No-charge pregnancy tests, 1996 and undated (Box CH30)
    - National Organization for Women (NOW) advertising, 1986 and 1988 (Box CH30)
    - NOW directory, 1997 (Box CH30)
    - Pamphlet and stationery design, 1996 and undated (Box CH30)
    - Pamphlets and Choices calendars, 1981 and undated (Box CH30)
    - Parke-Davis negotiations, 1998 (Box CH30)
    - Pennsylvania marketing letters, 1994 (Box CH30)
    - Phone book advertising, 1997-1999 and undated, 2 folders (Box CH30)
    - Physicians marketing program, 1996 (Box CH30)
    - Public relations proposal, Cohn and Wolfe, 1996 (Box CH30)
    - Queens Health Care Market Study, 1995-1996 and undated (Box CH30)
    - Radio advertising - Mental Health Center, 1996-1998 (Box CH30)
    - Radio advertising, 1982, 1996 and undated, 2 folders (Box CH30)
    - Relocation announcements, 1998 (Box CH30)
    - RSK Advertising, 1997-1998 (Box CH30)
    - Statistics, "Radio calls," [1995-1996] (Box CH30)
    - Subway advertising, 1996 (Box CH30)
    - Subway poster, 1999 (Box CH30)
    - Utilization statistics and marketing plan, 1989-1990 and undated (Box CH30)
    - Web site work, Sara Yager, 1998 (Box CH30)
  - Operations Subseries, 1970-2000 and undated
    This largest subseries in the Choices Series is divided into Facilities, Mental Health, New York Government, Personnel, and General Operations. It contains files related to the day-to-day operations and policies of Choices Women's Medical Center, and includes meeting minutes; procedural manuals; material on medical policies and problems; files on various contractors and outside service providers; and other administrative material. Files are arranged chronologically within each category.
    The New York Government files include assessments of Choices's medical services by various state and city agencies, often as part of the Medicaid review process. Note that folder titles in the New York Government group refer to the New York State government unless otherwise specified. The Mental Health files include records of Choices's Rape Treatment Program in the early 1990s and its Mental Health Center in the mid- to late 1990s. The Personnel files deal with personnel policies, staff training, and staff events.
    Personnel files for individual employees can be found in the Personnel Subseries. Additional administrative records can be found in the Staff Files Subseries.
    - Facilities, 1977-1998 and undated
      - 1977-1978, Relocation and lease (Box CH30)
      - 1977-1978 and undated, New York State Department of Health relocation application, 1 of 2 folders (Box CH30)
      - 1977-1978 and undated, New York State Department of Health relocation application, 2 of 2 folders (Box CH31)
      - 1977-1996 and undated, Leases (Box CH31)
      - 1985-1989, Richard F. Hein architects (Box CH31)
      - 1987-1988, Robbery (Box CH31)
      - 1988, New York City Department of Buildings, code violations (Box CH31)
      - 1989, Estimated alterations costs (Box CH31)
      - 1989, Furnishings layout (Box CH31)
      - 1989, Medical records furniture estimates (Box CH31)
      - 1989 and undated, Renovation plans (Box CH31)
      - 1989, Renovation plans, tenth and eleventh floors (Box CH31)
      - circa 1990, Queens neighborhoods - demographic statistics (Box CH31)
      - 1990-1993, Construction notebook, 6 folders (Box CH31)
      - 1991-1993, Tres Construction, Inc. notebook, 3 folders (Box CH32)
      - 1991-1996 and undated, Renovations, 4 folders (Box CH32)
      - 1991-1998, Building management correspondence (Box CH32)
      - 1994, Environmental survey (Box CH32)